softwarehow.com 2018-09-12

# Privacy Policy

_This policy was last updated on Nov 1, 2015._

Thank you for visiting [SoftwareHow.com](https://www.softwarehow.com/) (hereinafter known as “provider,” “me” or “I” or “the site”).

Your privacy is very important. Accordingly, I have developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how I collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. If you require any more information or have any questions about this policy, please feel free to [contact me](https://www.softwarehow.com/contact/).

The following outlines specific policies for this site.

## Use of Cookies

When accessing this website, the owner will learn certain information about you during your visit. Similar to other commercial Web sites, the site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and Web server logs to collect information about how this website is used. Information gathered through cookies and logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at this site.

## Third-party Links

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the content or privacy of such other sites. I encourage you to be aware when you leave the site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Email Information

If you choose to correspond with the site owner through email, the owner may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. The owner provides the same protections for these electronic communications that he employs in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone. This also applies when you register for this website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make a purchase on this site.

## IP Addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by this web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

## Use of Testimonials

In accordance to with [the FTC guidelines](https://www.ftc.gov/news-events/media-resources/truth-advertising/advertisement-endorsements) concerning the use of endorsements and testimonials in advertising, please be aware of the following:

Testimonials that appear on this site are actually received via text, audio or video submission. They are individual experiences, reflecting real life experiences of those who have used the mentioned products and/or services in some way. They are individual results and results do vary. The site owner does not claim that they are typical results. The testimonials are not necessarily representative of all of those who will use our products and/or services.

The testimonials displayed in any form on this site (text, audio, video or other) are reproduced verbatim, except for correction of grammatical or typing errors. Some may have been shortened. SoftwareHow.com is not responsible for any of the opinions or comments posted on the site.

## How The Site Owner Will Use Them

The site owner may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To help create and publish content most relevant to you.
  * To provide feedback in an online survey.
  * To participate in promotional offers.
  * To deliver services that you request or purchase.
  * To alert you of special offers, updated information and other new services.

### About Policy Changes

The site owner reserves the rights to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, the owner will not use the personal information you have submitted under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

### Contact

If you have any questions about these policies, please [address them](https://www.softwarehow.com/contact/) to the site owner.
